感觉太舒服了
Oh, that feels so good.
哎呀  我运气真好
Oh, lucky me.
有咖啡喝还可以看现场性爱演出
Coffee and a live sex show.
不好意思  你说什么
l'm sorry, what?
不好意思
l'm sorry.
没事  我只是在念书给艾玛听
Nothing. l was just reading to Emma.
念《时尚》杂志吗
From Cosmo?
是啊  是啊  是…
Yeah. Yeah, it's:
《让你有更细致的肌肤》
''Climax Your Way to Better Skin.''
我今天必须要去买衣服
So l have to go shopping today,
这真是我最不喜欢做的事
which is my least favorite thing.
我实在是很不会挑选衣服
l'm so bad at picking out clothes.
所以你需要有很了解
So you need someone who knows fashion
时尚的人来给你建议
to tell you what looks good.
不要是我...
Not me...
嘿  瑞秋
Oh, hey, Rach?
怎样
Yeah?
或许你可以带查莉去买衣服
Maybe you could take Charlie shopping?
喔  嗯…
Oh, well....
你可能很忙没空吧
l'm sure you have better things to do.
你在开玩笑吗
You kidding?
瑞秋爱死逛街了
Rachel loves to shop,
而且她品味极佳
and she has great taste.
就是她教我在劳动节之后
She's the one that taught me,
不要穿白色衣服
you don't wear white after Labor Day...
而且永远永远记住
...and to always, always, always
在试穿衣服时一定要穿内衣裤
put on underwear when trying on clothes.
如果你有空
lf you have the time,
我真的需要你的帮忙
l'd really appreciate the help.
好的  好啊  我们逛街去
Okay. Yeah, let's shop.
好的  你一定会
Okay, you are gonna come back
买回来很多有格调的衣服
with some very classy clothes.
还有一些淫荡的内衣  淫荡喔
And some slutty lingerie. Slutty!
好的  太好了  拜拜
Okay, great. All right, bye.
烦死了
Pain in the ass!
已经挂掉了  对吧
That's off, right?
怎么了  菲比
What's the matter, Pheebs?
迈克的姐姐刚邀请我
Mike's sister just invited me
去今晚的派对
to a party tonight
而且他也会去
and he's gonna be there.
她说  "别担心
She was like, ''Don't worry.
我问过他了
l asked him
完全不介意见到你"
and he's totally okay with seeing you.''
所以现在我一定得去了
So now l have to go so he'll think
以便让他感觉我完全不介意见他
that l'm totally okay with seeing him.
你根本就很介意
Which you're not.
因为你还没有忘记他
Because you're hung up on him.
没错
Exactly.
你想要他懊悔不已
You want him to eat his heart out,
所以你一定要看起来艳光四射
so you have to look fabulous.
我根本没有那样想过
l didn't even think about that.
性别政治
Sexual politics!
菲比  我要带查莉去逛街
Pheebs, l'm taking Charlie shopping.
一起来  我可以帮你挑衣服
Come and l'll help you find something.
太棒了
That'd be great.
真是太好了  你们三个人
Oh, isn't that nice? The three of you,
一起试穿淫荡睡衣
trying on slutty lingerie together.
我们没有要那样做
That's not what we're gonna do.
你为什么要打断我
Why'd you ruin it?
我这么想会伤害到谁
Who was l hurting?
《老友记》  第九季 第22集  精子捐献者
Friends S09E22 The One With The Donor
还好她长得很漂亮
Fortunately, she has a very pretty face.
我还是无法相信
l still can't believe this.
我的子宫是不适着床的环境
My uterus is an inhospitable environment?
我一直都很努力
l've always tried so hard
想要当个称职的女主人
to be a good hostess.
我不敢相信我的精子的活动力太低
l can't believe my sperm have low motility.
告诉你  当我在长大的时候
Because let me tell you, while l was growing up,
它们倒是等不及要到处去游玩
they sure seemed to be in a hurry to get places.
嗨
Hi there.
Hi.
关于你们上星期的测试我很抱歉
l'm sorry there wasn't better news
没有什么更好的消息
from your tests last week...
但是我想要跟你们谈谈
...but l wanted to talk to you
你们可有的选择
about your options.
好的
Okay.
首先
Well,first of all.
虽然你们以正常方式
Even though your chances of conceiving
受孕的机率很低…
through natural means aren't great...
但是很难定论的
...you never know,
所以你们还是持续进行性生活
so keep having sex on a regular basis.
哦  不要
Oh, damn it!
别担心
Don't worry.
等一下你就会习惯了
After a while, you'll tune it out.
在这种情况之下
Given your situation,
最佳的选择就是…
the options with the greatest chances for success...
代孕母亲或是经由捐赠精子受孕
...would be surrogacy or insemination using a sperm donor.
好吧
Ok.
如果你们认为上述
lf you feel that neither of those
两种选择都不适合
is right for you,
你们还是可以选择领养
you could always adopt.
这是个暗示吗
ls that a hint?
我们是很爱你的  唐纳利医生
Because we love you, Dr.Connelly,
但是我们不想要领养你
but we don't want you to be our child.
喔
Wow!
还说别人的环境不好客
Talk about an inhospitable environment.
嗨  你准备好要去接菲比
Hi. Okay, you ready to go pick up Phoebe
逛街了吗
and go shopping?
我们走吧
Let's do it.
好的  祝你们逛得愉快
All right, have a good time.
那里面是找不到衣服的
Not gonna find any clothes in there.
你们好
Hey, you guys.
嗨
Hi.
猜猜看谁是
Guess who's up for keynote speaker
全国古生物学大会的主讲人
at the National Paleontology Conference?
克里斯·培利
Chris Bailey?
对啊  是啊
Yeah, right.
他上次准时提交
When was the last time
摘要是什么时候呢
he made a submission deadline for an abstract?
你为什么要笑呢
Why are you laughing?
只是想了解一下
Just seeing what it'd be like
当古生物学家是怎样的
to be a paleontologist.
真好玩  是啊
lt's fun. Yeah.
所以你要当主讲人
So you're up for keynote speaker?
是谁做的决定呢
Who's deciding?
薛曼教授
Professor Sherman.
我今天要跟他见面
l'm meeting with him today.
要想感动他可不容易
He's a pretty tough guy to impress.
我知道怎么让他惊奇
l think l know how to dazzle him.
你应该不会是要变个魔术
You're not gonna to do a magic trick,
对吧
are you?
不是
No.
大家好
Hey, guys.
等一下
Wait a minute, you guys.
我想要问你们一个问题
l want to ask you something.
我可能会在这个古生物学大会演说
l may get to speak at this paleontology convention.
如果是这样  我想邀请你们
lf l do, l'd love for you guys
来听我的演讲
to come and hear me.
我想我们肯定会因为有家庭
l think l can safely say that
工作或是身体不适等理由而去不成
we all have family issues, work and/or are sick.
是在巴巴多斯
lt's in Barbados.
但是你是最重要的
But you come first.
我去定了
l'm there.
待会见
See you later.
好的  拜
Okay, bye.
拜  再见
Bye. See you.
拜
Bye.
验孕诊所怎么说
So how did it go at the fertility clinic?
不像上次一样好玩
Not as much fun as last time.
很明显地  他们只有在采精子样本时
Apparently, you only get porn
才会给你看色情书刊
if you're giving a sperm sample.
那医生怎么说呢
So, what did the doctor say?
可以用代孕母亲  但莫妮卡这一辈子
There's surrogacy, but Monica's dreamt
都在梦想怀孕…
her whole life of carrying a child...
而她会觉得看着代孕母亲怀孕
...and she just felt that watching
对她而言会太难受了
a surrogate would be too hard for her.
所以你们不考虑代理孕母
So you're ruling out surrogacy?
没错
Yeah.
所以我不用知道那是什么意思
So l don't have to learn what that means?
除了领养外
Aside from adoption,
剩下的选择就是接受精子捐赠
the only other choice is insemination...
所以我们现在在讨论精子捐赠者的事
...so we're talking about sperm donors.
够了  我随时为你效劳  兄弟
Enough said. l'm there for you, man.
她在哪  楼上吗
Where is she, upstairs?
那你的感觉呢
So how do you feel about all this?
我真希望我们有
l wish there was an easier way
更简单的方式可生孩子
for us to have a child,
但是我们并没有选择
but there isn't one.
别这样  罗斯  做做好人
Come on, Ross, be a good guy.
挺身而出吧
Step up and do it.
什么
What?
什么  不   我不会把本给他们的
What?! No! l'm not gonna give them Ben!
我们从核磁共振成像
The data we're receiving
跟脱氧核糖核酸测试所取得的化石...
from MRl scans and DNA testing...
资料数据是很惊人的
...of these fossils are staggering.
我的意思是我们一直以来都将
l mean, we've been accepting
李奇年代法视为理所当然
Leakey's dates as a given.
但是如果它的误差
But if they're off
即使只有十万年左右…
by even a 100,000 years or so...
那你可以舍弃我们大部分推论…
...then you can just throw most of our assumptions...
你知道的  丢到垃圾桶里
...you know, right in the trash.
所以  我要说的是…
So, what l'm saying is....
是…
ls that....
是所受影响的后果是很大的
ls that repercussions could be huge.
我是说  不只是在古生物学
l mean, not just in paleontology,
但是如果你仔细想想…
but if you think about it...
甚至是在进化生物学  基因学  地质学
...in evolutionary biology, genetics, geology.
我是说  真的  无限想像的空间
l mean, truly, the mind boggles.
嗯  结果不该是这样的
Well, that's not what you want.
试试"男人的诱惑"香水
lncentive for Men?
我要喷一点
l'll take some of that.
菲比  那是男生的香水
Pheebs, that's for men.
我知道
l know.
在我等一下去派对时...
When l go to the party later...
迈克会知道我已经忘了他了
...Mike will know l'm over him
因为我闻起来会有另一个男人的味道
because l'll smell like another guy.
好了
Okay.
太好了  我在跟俄罗斯计程车司机约会
Oh, good, l'm dating a Russian cabdriver.
拜托  有人买这个吗
Seriously, does anyone buy this?
这闻起来像是甜菜
l smell like beets.
你知道吗
So, you know what,
我真的很喜欢
l really like those jackets
那些有垫肩的外套
with the shoulder pads in them.
你觉得哪里有呢
Where do you think those would be?
梅兰妮·葛丽芬在《上班女郎》里面穿的
On Melanie Griffith in Working Girl.
我想你适合穿的在这边
l think what you want is over here.
我就知道  我需要有人帮我
See, l told you l needed someone.
对了  为了要谢谢你
By the way, as a thank you,
我真的很想请你吃饭
l would really love to take you out.
真的吗
Really?
是啊
Yeah!
乔伊跟我
Actually Joey and I
今晚要去看电影
are going to the movies tonight,
你想要一起去吗
wanna come?
我不行
Oh, l can't.
因为我看过了
Because l've seen them.
你已经看过所有的电影了
You've seen all the movies?
是啊  我是铁杆粉丝
Yeah. l'm a big fan.
电影的
Of the movies.
移动的画面
You know, motion pictures.
有声电影
The talkies.
瑞秋
Rach,
你可以跟我进去试衣间试穿吗
will you come with me to a dressing room?
当然
Sure.
好的
Okay.
或许我们可以做别的事
Maybe we could do something else.
你知道的  那要看是什么事
You know, that depends on what it is.
很多东西我都做过了
l've done a lot of stuff.
你刚刚是怎么了
So, what were you doing out there?
你不喜欢查莉吗
Do you not like Charlie?
她还好啦
She's okay.
我不知道
l don't know,
我只是跟她不投缘吧
l just don't get a really good vibe from her.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
l don't know.
你知道的  只是她的一举一动
You know, just the way
聪明的要命...
she waltzed in here all smart...
而且又高挑  你知道的...
...and tall, you know...
让乔伊拜倒在她的石榴裙下
...and just swept Joey off his feet.
别人都没有机会
Nobody else has a chance.
还有谁呢
Who else?
任何人啊
Anybody.
你  我
You. Me.
你知道的  莫妮卡的妈
You know, Monica's mom.
你喜欢乔伊
You like Joey?!
菲比
Phoebe!
好吧  你说的没错
All right, look, l do.
我对他是有一点点感觉  只是...
l have a little thing for him. Just--
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
是肉欲的
lt's just physical.
我已经完全控制住了  好吗
l have it totally under control, okay?
只是当我看到他们在一起...
lt's just when l see them together...
有时候  我就会有点忌妒
...sometimes, l just get a little jealous.
哇  好讽刺喔  他以前喜欢你过
Wow. lsn't that ironic that he liked you,
然后现在你喜欢…
and now you like--?
我知道
l get it!
好吧  一切都控制住就好了
All right, as long as it's under control.
你不可以采取任何行动
You can't do anything about it.
他已经跟她在一起了
He's already dating her.
她是个好人
She is a nice person.
那是不对的
That wouldn't be right.
我知道  我知道  所以没事啦
l know, l know. So it's just not a big deal.
你可以不要说出去吗
So can we keep this between us?
当然
Sure.
太好了  因为我得出去了
Great, because l gotta get out of here.
我快被甜菜味熏死了
The smell of beets is killing me.
查莉可能会有耳聋的双胞胎妹妹吗
Any chance Charlie has a deaf twin?
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, honey.
嘿
Hey.
我带个朋友回来吃晚餐
l brought a friend home for dinner.
这是我同事柴克
This is Zack from work.
当然啦
Oh, of course.
很高兴再见到你  柴克
lt's so nice to see you again, Zack.
我也是
You too.
你们并没有见过面
You guys haven't actually met before.
天啊  你们还真有礼貌
But, boy, you're both polite.
请坐  我帮你拿啤酒
Have a seat. l'll get you a beer.
我来拿
l got it.
谢谢
Thanks.
柴克不错吧
So Zack's pretty nice, huh?
是啊  应该吧
Yeah, l guess.
那你想不想要生个小孩
So how would you like to have a baby
一半儿你的  一半儿他的
that's half yours and half his?
什么
Excuse me?
我们在讲的是精子捐赠者
We're talking about sperm donors,
而柴克或许就是适当的人选
and Zack may be the guy.
他很聪明  健康
Look. He's intelligent, he's healthy,
体格强壮
he's athletic.
我是说  他是最佳"精"选了
l mean, he's sperm-tastic!
钱德勒  这太疯狂了
Chandler, this is crazy.
你是怎么跟他说的
Well, what did you even say to him?
"上来看看我老婆
''Come up. Meet my wife.
给我们你的精子"
Give us your sperm.''
我邀请他来吃晚餐
l invited him to dinner
让你有机会了解他
so you'd get a chance to get to know him.
如果我们去精子银行
I mean, if we go through with a sperm bank,
我们根本不能见到那个捐赠者
you never meet the guy,
也查不到他的底细
get to check him out.
钱德勒
Chandler!
我告诉你  他非常棒
l'm telling you, he's great.
我是说  即使我的精子没有问题
l mean, even if my sperm worked fine,
我也认为我们应该选择他
l think he'd be the way to go.
这事情我不参加
l'm not going to be a part of this.
你不能随便带个男的回来
You can't bring some random guy home
就想让我接受他当精子捐赠者
and expect him to be our sperm donor.
好吧
Okay.
柴克
Zack?
谢谢
Thanks.
你有杯垫吗
Do you have a coaster?
我不想在桌上留下印记
l don't want to make a ring.
跟我说说你的情况  柴克
Tell me about yourself, Zack.
天啊  你觉得她听到了吗
Oh, God, do you think she heard?
如果她听到就惨了
lt'd be so bad if she heard.
或许她没有听到
Maybe she didn't hear.
我到隔壁间说话
l'll go into that dressing room and talk.
你待在这里
You stay in here.
看看你是不是可以听到我说话
and I'll talk and see if you can hear me.
好的
Okay, great.
噢  感谢上帝
Oh, thank God,
我听不到你说话
l can't hear a word that you're saying.
我还没有开始说话
l didn't say anything yet.
那回去里面然后说话啊
Well, get back in there and talk.
我是瑞秋
l'm Rachel.
让艾玛在电话上
lt's so annoying
跟我朋友讲话
when l put Emma on the phone
真的很讨厌
to talk with my friends.
什么
What?
有些事是很难
Well, some things are just hard
当你的面说的
to say to your face.
好吧  我听到了
Okay, well, l heard that.
表示她也听到了
Which means that she heard it too.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
我们该怎么办呢
Oh, what are we gonna do?
就老实跟她说吧
Just be honest with her.
噢  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
父母让婴儿听电话
And it is annoying when parents
的确是很讨厌
put their baby on the phone...
好了  你说够了
All right, enough out of you!
喂
Hello?
我要跟查莉讲话
l need to talk to Charlie.
她在吗
ls she there?
不在  她跟瑞秋去逛街了
No, she went shopping with Rachel.
找她干嘛  怎么了
Why? What's up?
我正在跟薛曼教授
l'm meeting with Professor Sherman
讨论关于我当主讲人的事
about my being the keynote speaker.
进行的如何呢
How's it going?
可以更顺利的
lt could be better.
他睡着了
He fell asleep.
什么  但是我已经
What? But l already bought
订了到百慕大的机票了
my ticket to Bermuda!
是巴巴多斯
Barbados.
好啦  我再租车开过去
Fine, l'll rent a car and drive.
你一定要得到这工作
You have to get that job.
我应该怎么办呢
What am l supposed to do?
他完全睡着了
He's out cold.
事实上
ln fact,
刚刚他还在说梦话
he was just talking in his sleep before...
而且他还要一个叫法兰的人
...and evidently he wants someone named Fran
"再打大力点"
to ''spank him harder.''
那叫醒他吧
Well, just wake him up.
不可以
l can't.
如果他发现我是让他睡着的人
lf he realizes that l'm the one
我就得不到这个工作了
who put him to sleep, l won't get the job.
那倒是挺难的
That's a tough one.
等等
Oh, wait a minute.
这以前也发生在我身上过
This happened to me before.
是啊  我之前在试演一出戏剧的时候
Yeah, l was auditioning for a play,
那个制作人睡着了  我...
and the producer fell asleep. l--
不  等等
No, wait a minute.
其实是我睡着了
lt was me who fell asleep.
我是说  莎士比亚
l mean, hey, Shakespeare,
来点动作场面吧
how about a chase scene once in a while?
嘿  晚餐好了
Hey, guys, dinner's ready.
我先去洗手
l'm gonna go wash up first.
谢了
Thanks.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我要我的孩子有他的基因
l want his genes for my kid.
那双眼睛  那颧骨
Those eyes, those cheekbones.
好了  你要分清你是过度狂热
Okay, there's enthusiastic,
还是你是个同性恋
and there's just plain gay.
你不喜欢他
You don't like him.
我觉得他还不错
l think he's fine.
但是我们对他了解不够
But we don't know anything real about him.
我希望我们可以知道多一点
l wish we could get more information.
好的  跟着我的话锋转
All right, just follow my lead.
你们家真是好棒
You guys have a great place here.
谢谢  我很喜欢这地方
Thanks. l'm crazy about our place.
嘿  说到疯狂...
Hey, speaking of crazy...
你们家有人
...do you have a history
有人得过精神病吗
of mental illness in the family?
没有  但是我是有个叔叔
No. Although, l did have an uncle
投票给杜凯吉斯
who voted for Dukakis.
那真的不是我们
That's really not the kind of thing
期待的  柴克
we're looking for.Zack.
好的
Okay.
告诉我  你们是怎么认识的呢
So tell me, how'd you guys meet?
刚开始是朋友  在伦敦喝醉
Oh, friends first, drunk in London,
你知道的
you know the story.
我有个更棒的问题要问你
l've got a better question for you:
你或是你的血亲
Do you or any of your
有人有糖尿病吗
blood relatives have diabetes?
没有
No.
心脏病  老年痴呆症  痛风
Heart disease? Alzheimer's? Gout?
你们不常请朋友
You guys don't have people
到家里用餐  是吗
for dinner a lot, huh?
我们只是在找话题聊聊
We're just making conversation.
好吧  我今天听到一个笑话
Yeah, well, okay. l heard a joke today.
真的是挺好笑的
lt's pretty funny.
你知道有什么是不好笑的吗
You know what's not funny?
雄性秃头
Male pattern baldness.
你们今晚对我很有兴趣
You guys have shown a lot of interest in me tonight,
我很受宠若惊
and l'm flattered...
而且老实说  是有点害怕
...and quite frankly, a little frightened.
我们可以聊聊别的话题吗
Can we just talk about something else?
当然
Sure.
好的
All right.
这个意大利小方饺真是美味
This ravioli's delicious.
我发现你享用那水饺的
l notice you're enjoying that ravioli
牙齿真是整齐
with a beautiful set of teeth.
你小时候有戴牙套吗
Did you have braces as a child?
不  没有
No, l didn't.
太好了
Yes!
我们很重视牙齿的  柴克
We're teeth people, Zack.
好吧  我们就这么做了
All right.Let's just do it.
我们过去问她有没有听到
Let's just go over there and see if she heard.
好主意
Good plan.
好的
Okay.
什么  你要去哪
What? Where are you going?
对不起  瑞秋
Oh, l'm sorry, Rachel.
我没有时间
l don't have time
玩你的幼稚游戏  好吗
for your childish games, okay?
我还得要找到
l still have to find
很惊艳的衣服穿
something incredible to wear...
那我才可以在"谁先忘了谁"上
...so l can beat Mike
打败迈克
at ''Who's More Over Who'' !
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
去试穿衣服
Trying on clothes.
真的吗  在试衣间吗
Oh, really? ln the dressing room?
喔  真奇怪
Well, that's so weird.
菲比跟我刚刚也在试衣间
Phoebe and l were in the dressing room.
天啊  这世界真是小
Gosh, it's just such a small world.
瑞秋  我听到你们俩的对谈了
Rachel, l heard you two guys whispering.
天啊  你听到了
Oh, God, you did, you heard.
好的  听着  让我解释
Okay, look, let me explain.
没有必要解释
There's nothing to explain.
我都听到了
l heard you.
菲比喜欢乔伊
Phoebe likes Joey.
是啊
Yeah.
我不明白
l don't understand it.
我是说菲比喜欢乔伊
l mean, Phoebe likes Joey...
可是她却来买衣服
...and then she's here to buy a dress
来惊艳另一个男人
to impress another guy?
是啊  菲比就是那样
Yeah, that's Phoebe.
她就是那样 你知道的
That's Phoebe. You know,
她就是全部都要
she just wants them all.
那就像是女花痴
lt's, like, she's nympho.
哇
Wow!
是啊
Yeah.
对了  另外
You know, by the way,
我有听到你告诉她不可以做任何事
l heard you tell her not to do anything.
谢谢你替我说话
Thanks for sticking up for me.
天啊  你真是个好人
God, you are such a nice person.
我尽量
l try.
我的天啊  你真的要我
Oh, my God, you really want me
当主讲人吗
to be the keynote speaker?
谢谢你
Thank you!
不用客气
You're welcome.
哇  你辣到...
Wow! You look...
都能让我把手里的食物放下了
...stop-eating hot!
这是最高阶段的辣哦
Which is like the highest level of hotness.
你确定吗
Okay, are you sure?
因为我真的很恐惧这场派对
Because l am really dreading going to this party.
那就别去啊
Then don't go.
迈克知道我要去
Mike knows l'm coming.
如果我没出现
lf l don't show up,
他会以为那是因为他...
he'll think it's because of him...
我那样就会很没面子
...and then l'm gonna lose face.
这对我来说是很严重的事
That's a very serious thing in my culture.
好吧  那就去派对吧
All right, then you go to that party,
然后假装已经完全忘记迈克了
and you pretend to be over Mike.
之后你再来我家
Afterward, you come to my place
我再帮你好好借酒解愁
and l'll get you good and drunk.
没问题  好的
You got it. Okay.
但是不要喝你自己酿的酒好吗
But not on the wine that you made, okay?
因为我不想要
Because l just don't want to
再进急诊室了
go back to the emergency room.
大卫
David?
菲比  嗨
Phoebe! Hi.
噢  我的天
Oh, my God!
嗨
Hi.
你简直也太漂亮了
Wow! You look unbelievable.
哦  是啊  嗯...
Oh, yeah, well....
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?
我从明斯克回来了  永远回来了
Well, l'm back from Minsk. Permanently.
发生什么事呢
Well, what happened?
记得我曾尝试完成...
Remember how l was trying to achieve...
次原子阳电子净化吗
...the positronic distillation of subatomic particles?
是啊
Yeah.
在经过八年的研究之后
Well, after eight years of research,
我发现...
l discovered...
那是做不到的
...that it can't be done.
嗯...
Well...
你终于回来了真是好
...great that you're back.
你好吗
How are you?
很好  过得还不错
Good. Good. Life is good.
很好
Good.
我现在有交往的对象了
Well, l'm seeing someone.
这样啊  恭喜你了
Good for you.
是啊
Yeah.
她也是科学家
She's also a scientist,
很聪明也很漂亮
so she's very smart and pretty and....
而且事实上是因为你
lt's actually because of you really
我们才在一起的
that we're together.
我是说  我看到你
l mean, l saw what you had
跟那个迈克在一起
with that Mike guy...
然后我告诉自己  "天啊  我也想要那样"
...and l just said, ''Boy, l want that.''
麦克跟我分手了
Mike and l broke up.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
因为我没有在跟谁交往
Because l'm not seeing anybody.
我完全是编出来的
l just totally made that up.
真的吗
Really?
我不知道为什么瞎编
l don't know why,
我很抱歉
l'm sorry.
我猜我只是不想没面子
l guess l just didn't want to lose face.
我能了解
l understand.
是啊  好的  那...
Yeah. Okay. So then, okay....
我们都住在纽约
So we're both living in New York,
没有交往对象
not seeing anyone.
这太不像我们了
That's so not like us.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, l know.
嗯  这或许是个蠢问题
Well, this is probably a stupid question,
看到你穿这样...s
seeing that you look like that...
但是你现在
...but do you have someplace
有要去什么地方吗
that you need to be right now?
嗯...
Well....
没有
No.
那你想不想去喝点东西呢
Well, do you want to get a drink?
我很想
l'd love to.
太棒了
Great.
好的
Okay.
你有闻到甜菜味吗
Do you smell beets?
好吧  站到我的上风边
All right, stay upwind of me.
嘿  那是菲比
Hey, there's Phoebe.
跟她在一起的是迈克
ls that Mike she's with?
不是  那是大卫
No, that's David.
还有第三个男人
There's a third guy?
只是冰山的一角
Tip of the iceberg.
我现在要走了
l'm gonna take off now.
你们会让我回家吗
You're gonna let me go home, aren't you?
你确定不要再多坐一下吗
Sure you don't want to stay a little longer?
不了  我应该要回家了
No, l should get home.
我有点累
l'm kind of tired.
你是刚感觉累吗
Are you just tired now?
还是一直都感觉累
Or are you always tired?
因为这很有可能是
Because that could be
忧郁症的前兆
a sign of clinical depression.
不  只是要想出我祖父母
No, it's tiring to figure out the age at
是几岁过世的让我很累
which all my grandparents died.
明天见
l'll see you tomorrow.
好的
Okay.
再见
Bye.
我想我们找到我们的精子了
l think we found our sperm.
他看起来是挺完美的
He does seem pretty perfect.
你也这么认为吗
Yeah? You think so?
我要开口问他吗
Should l ask him?
不要
No.
为什么呢
Why not?
就只因为
Just because his
他曾祖母有肥胖症吗
great-grandmother was obese?
反正我们的孩子也是会从你那遗传到的
Our kid's gonna get that from you anyway.
不  不是那个原因
No, that's not it.
只是在我们问他
lt's just that when we were asking him
那些问题时…
all those questions before...
我意识到我并不在乎
...l just realized l don't care
他是不是世上最完美的男人
if he is the most perfect guy in the world.
他不是你
He's not you.
是啊  他比我更好
Yeah, he's better!
不  他不是
No, he's not.
如果我不能跟你怀孕
lf l can't get pregnant with you,
我也不想跟他...
then l don't want to get pregnant by him...
或是跟任何人
...or anyone else.
真的  你确定吗
Really? Are you sure?
是的  我确定
Yeah, l'm sure.
感谢上帝
Thank God,
因为我也不想这样做
because l don't wanna do this either.
我会这样做
l was just doing it
是因为我以为你想这样
because l thought that was what you wanted.
我是丈夫
You know, l'm the husband.
我理当要提供精子的
l'm supposed to bring the sperm.
这实在是很体贴
That is so sweet.
我爱你
l love you.
所以你知道我们唯一的选择就只剩...
So you know this leaves us with....
领养
Adoption.
你觉得如何呢
How do you feel about that?
我想我没问题
l think l feel okay about it.
事实上我觉得非常的好
Actually, l think l feel really good about it.
我也是
Me too.
我想找到一个需要家庭温暖的小孩
l wanna find a baby that needs a home,
然后跟你一起抚养他
and l wanna raise it with you.
然后我想用我们
And l wanna mess it up
自己的方式来乱养他
in our own specific way.
我们就这么决定了
So this is it?
我们真的要领养
We're really gonna adopt?
是的
Yeah.
我的天  我们要当父母亲了
Oh, my God! We're gonna be parents!
我们会是很棒的父母
We are gonna be great parents.
而且可能会很快
And it could be soon.
我是说  想想看
l mean, think about it.
就是现在  在外面某个地方...
Right now, somewhere out there...
我们的孩子可能正被受孕
...our baby could be being conceived.
等等  如果我们够幸运
Wait. lf we're lucky,
而且我们真的  真的  真的很安静…
and we're really, really, really quiet...
我们或许可以听到
...we may be able to hear
保险套破裂的声音
the sound of a condom breaking.
嘿  柴克
Hey, Zack.
嘿  钱德勒
Hey, Chandler.
我想为昨晚的事道歉
l wanted to apologize for last night.
我感到我们让你很不舒服
l got the feeling we made you a little uncomfortable.
不  并没有
No, you didn't.
真的吗
Really?
没错  你们是有
No, you did.
我老婆跟我越界了
My wife and l have some boundary issues.
有时候我们会问些很不适当的问题
Sometimes we ask inappropriate questions.
我们正在改进中
We're working on it.
这些是星期五推销会的看板
Here are the boards for Friday's pitch.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知不知道珍娜
You wouldn't know if Jeanette's planning on
是否要留着她的孩子
keeping her baby, would you?